A story about the people you love, and how to survive them.
Ella McCay is a comedy, drama film directed by James L. Brooks.
An idealistic young politician juggles familial issues and a challenging work life while
preparing to take over the job of her mentor, the state’s longtime incumbent governor.
Ella McCay, played by Emma Mackey.
Helen McCay, played by Jamie Lee Curtis.
Governor Bill, played by Albert Brooks.
Casey McCay, played by Spike Fearn.
Eddie McCay, played by Woody Harrelson.
Claire McCay, played by Rebecca Hall.
Ella McCay is a 2025 American political comedy-drama
film written and directed by James L.
The film stars Emma Mackey in the title role with Jamie Lee Curtis, Jack Lowden, Kumail Nanjiani, Ayo
Edebiri, Spike Fearn, Julie Kavner, Rebecca Hall, Albert Brooks, and Woody Harrelson.
Ella McCay premiered at the El Capitan Theatre on December 9, 2025, and was
released in the United States by 20th Century Studios on December 12.
The film received unfavorable reviews from critics and
grossed $4.56 million on a $35 million budget.
The film explores themes of politics, aunt,
dysfunctional family, political scandal, governer.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.